[
    {
        "id": 0,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "Which is the Smallest Country in the World?",
        "a": "Maldives",
        "b": "Monaco",
        "c": "Vatican City",
        "d": "Montenegro",
        "answer": "c"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "What is the currency of the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia?",
        "a": "Riyal",
        "b": "Dinaar",
        "c": "Dirham",
        "d": "Shekel",
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "Which of these edible items is not the leaf of a plant?",
        "a": "Tea",
        "b": "Coffee",
        "c": "Spinach",
        "d": "Lettuce",
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "Which sport is Pete Sampras associated with professionally?",
        "a": "Golf",
        "b": "Tennis",
        "c": "Hockey",
        "d": "Boxing",
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "Which of these is not an Ape?",
        "a": "Gorilla",
        "b": "Chimpanzee",
        "c": "Orangutan",
        "d": "Monkey",
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "difficulty": 1,
        "question": "What does the 'C' in VCR stand for?",
        "a": "Cassette",
        "b": "Compact",
        "c": "Cable",
        "d": "Cinema",
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "Who was the first person to reach North Pole?",
        "a": "Robert Peary",
        "b": "Robert Cook",
        "c": "Charles Hillary",
        "d": "Johan Don",
        "answer": "a"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "difficulty": 2,
        "question": "Who the First Prime Minister of Britain?",
        "a": "John Blunt",
        "b": "Henry Waterloo",
        "c": "George Bush",
        "d": "Robert Walpole",
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "Which country won the First Football World Cup?",
        "a": "Brazil",
        "b": "Uruguay",
        "c": "Belgium",
        "d": "Argentina",
        "answer": "b"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "difficulty": 4,
        "question": "Who was the first female cosmonaut in Space?",
        "a": "Peggy Whitson",
        "b": "Svetlana Savitskaya",
        "c": "Sally Ride",
        "d": "Velentina Tereshkova",
        "answer": "d"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "difficulty": 3,
        "question": "Where is The Engadin Valley located?",
        "a": "Egypt",
        "b": "Portugal",
        "c": "Switzerland",
        "d": "Turkey",
        "answer": "c"
    }
]